{
    "id": "7931148b7f0949579bf6b038193e1a50",
    "title": "Active or Passive Voice",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6a7eaf15060440e18b64d6abf50111d7",
            "title": "Active Or Passive",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We .................................. this.",
                    "description": "When the subject is the doer of the action, we use an active verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will not tolerate",
                        "will not be tolerated",
                        "will not be tolerating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................. responsible for the failure of the project.",
                    "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
                    "answers": [
                        "held",
                        "was held"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The prizes .................................... by the chief guest.",
                    "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
                    "answers": [
                        "distributed",
                        "were distributed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When mummy arrived, the problem .....................................",
                    "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
                    "answers": [
                        "resolved",
                        "was resolved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... to him yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "talked",
                        "was talked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ..................................... of the developments.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have informed",
                        "have been informed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ...................................... his bride to his friends.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "introduced",
                        "was introduced",
                        "has been introduced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... to a nice woman at the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "introduced",
                        "was introduced",
                        "have introduced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ..................................... for his kind deeds.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "still remembered",
                        "is still remembered",
                        "is still remembering"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everyone .................................. to hear the news.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shocked",
                        "has shocked",
                        "was shocked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We .......................................... anything from them yet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have not heard",
                        "have not been heard",
                        "have not been hearing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The girl .................................... by a passerby.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saved",
                        "was saved",
                        "was saving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}